Connor Kai-Ho Lee

connor.lee@yale.edu 626-377-5522

OBJECTIVE

Highly motivated college student at Yale university interested in gaining experience in social-robotics. Through my organization and communication skills, I can solve problems both independently and collaboratively. I have demonstrated reliable service and worthy contribution to the development of quality products and projects during my previous internships, and I would be a beneficial asset to your team.

EDUCATION

Yale University, New Haven, CT

2019 - Present

U.S. Citizen

Bachelor of Arts in Cognitive Science (2024)

- Cognitive Science Coursework: Thinking, Mental Lives of Babies and Animals, Mystery of Sleep, Intro to Cognitive Science
- CS Coursework: Intro to Information Systems, Computer Science & the Modern Intellectual Agenda

Loyola High School, Los Angeles, CA

2015 - 2019

Highschool Diploma

- Cum Laude
- Athlete of the Year (2019)
- PSAT Commended Scholar (2019)
- Loyola Men's Varsity Swim Team Captain (2018-2019)
- USA Swimming Scholastic All-American (2016-2019)

TECHNICAL PROFILE

Programming:

Python (2 years); HTML (1 year); CSS (1 year); MATLAB (<1 year); Swift (<1 year)

Platforms & Systems:

Windows; Mac OSX; Linux

• Microsoft Office Suite; Google's G Suite Adobe Photoshop

WORK EXPERIENCE

Schulte Research, Austin, TX (remote)

Research Intern

January 2021 - April 2021

- Spearheaded research on the new wave of PropTech startup companies by exploring venture capital firms' portfolios
- Acknowledged in Paul Schulte's book The Digital Transformation of Property in Greater China: Finance, 5G, Al, and Blockchain
- Produced comprehensive PowerPoints outlining company growth, business models, and market strategies
- Discussed viability of companies in terms of business objective, user platform, and practicality of technological tools.

LinQuest Corp., Los Angeles, CA (remote)

Finance Intern

May 2020 - December 2020

- · Created Excel spreadsheets to develop daily budget allocations and cost analysis spreadsheets for upcoming projects
- Used Salesforce to organize completed proposals and company expenditures for accessibility, visibility, and auditing
- Managed COVID-19 business interruption charge reports during the coronavirus pandemic ensuring employee efficiency

Yale University, New Haven, CT

Men's Swimming and Diving Member

Aug 2019 - Present

- 20 hours a week of training
- 2020 US Olympic Trials qualifier
- School record holder in 100 Butterfly and 50 Butterfly
- 2020 Ivy League Champion

Volunteering

Loyola Senior Service Project, Los Angeles, CA

2019

Aided teachers at an impoverished LA county elementary school by tutoring students in reading and writing

2016

Los Angeles Food Bank, Los Angeles, CA Packaged and sorted food items for distribution among underprivileged citizens living in LA County

2016

Baja Build, Tijuana, MX • Built a 2-story house and privy for a homeless woman with a team of 10 classmates and their fathers

LANGUAGES

English (Native)

INTERESTS

Star Wars, Skateboarding, Movies, Anime, Music, Traveling, LEGO

REFERENCES

Jim Henry, Robert J.H. Kiphuth Head Coach @ Yale Swimming & Diving james.henry@yale.edu

Paul Schulte, Founder @ Schulte Research paul@schulte-research.com